<Vertical id="interdisciplinary_activities" launchable="true">
  <!-- Opening screen -->
  <Markdown id="interdisciplinary_orientation">
## Welcome to the Interdisciplinary Studies Module

In this simulated internship at Community 360, you'll apply interdisciplinary analysis to understand the complex issue of high school dropout rates in the community.

Working with supervisor Lianne Park and your intern teammates, you'll investigate causes, review research from multiple disciplines, and develop evidence-based recommendations.
  </Markdown>
  <!-- GSU professor image -->
  <Image id="interdisciplinary_gsu_prof_image" src="images/GSU_prof.png" alt="Professor at Georgia State University" />

  <!-- Team directory navigator -->
  <Vertical id="interdisciplinary_team_members">
    <Markdown id="team_directory_intro">
## Comm360 Team Directory

Explore the team directory to learn about your colleagues for this project. Click on each person to see their role, experience, and skills.
    </Markdown>

    <Navigator id="interdisciplinary_team_navigator"
               title="Comm360 Team"
               preview="TeamPreview"
               detail="TeamDetail">
- id: ty
  name: Ty
  role: Intern Teammate
  photo: /content/sba/images/ty.png
  bio: Intern at Comm360 focusing on program evaluation and data analysis.
  experience: 6 months at Comm360
  skills: [Data Analysis, Research, Program Evaluation]

- id: peggy
  name: Peggy
  role: Intern Teammate
  photo: /content/sba/images/peggy.png
  bio: Intern specializing in community outreach and stakeholder engagement.
  experience: 4 months at Comm360
  skills: [Community Outreach, Communication, Project Management]

- id: lacy
  name: Lacy
  role: Intern Teammate
  photo: /content/sba/images/lacy.png
  bio: Intern with focus on program development and implementation strategies.
  experience: 5 months at Comm360
  skills: [Program Development, Strategic Planning, Implementation]

- id: lianne
  name: Lianne Park
  role: Supervisor/Mentor
  photo: /content/sba/images/lianne.png
  bio: Director of multiple programs at Comm360 with extensive experience in program evaluation and development. Presents findings to the PDE committee.
  experience: 5 years at Comm360
  skills: [Program Management, Leadership, Strategic Planning, Evaluation]

- id: anne
  name: Anne Hastings
  role: Chief Executive Officer
  photo: /content/sba/images/anne.png
  bio: CEO of Comm360, making ultimate decisions about programs and resources. Reports to the board of directors.
  experience: 8 years at Comm360, 15+ years leadership experience
  skills: [Executive Leadership, Strategic Decision Making, Resource Management, Organizational Development]
    </Navigator>
  </Vertical>

</Vertical>
